Guide to the Amos Vogel Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Films, 1896-2001
  - Subseries II.1: Film Files, 1896-1993
    - The Andromeda Strain, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Anemic Cinema, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Angel City, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Angular Momentum, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Another Sky, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Anticipation of the Night, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Antonia: A Portrait of the Woman, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Antonio-Das-Mortes, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - A Nous La Liberté, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - AOS, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Aparajito, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - The Apartment, 1968 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Apocalypse Now, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Apotheosis, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - A Propos de Nice, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Apprenticeship (or Trainees), 1966? (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Arabesque for Kenneth Anger, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Arab-Israeli Dialogue, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Archangel Gabriel, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Archaeology, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Argument, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Aries Contra Atlas, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Arnulf Rainer, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Arrabal, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Arsenal, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The Artist in the Big Top, Perplexed, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - As If It Were Yesterday, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - The Assassination of Trotsky, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - L'Assassino, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Les Astronautes, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Asylum, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - L'Atalante, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Atanor, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - At Land, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - At the Movies, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Attica, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - The Atom Strikes, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - À Tout Prendre, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - L'Aube des Damnes (The Twilight of the Damned), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - August and July, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Au Hasard Balthazar, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Auschwitz, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - L'Authentic Proces de Carl-Emmanuel Jung, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Authoritarian Politics in Stone, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - An Autumn Afternoon, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Autumn Fire, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Aves: Magnificent Frigate Bird, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - L'Avventura, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - The Axfight, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Aymara of Mamanani: The Spirit Possession of Alejandro, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Babycart in River Styx, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Baby Doll, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Ballad of John and Yoko, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Ballet Mecanique, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Banana I, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Bananas, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Band of Outsiders, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Baptism of Fire, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Barbara, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Barbarella, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Barclay Bath Brothel, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Baron Munchausen, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Barren Lives, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - The Barrier, undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Barry Lyndon, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - The Battle of Chile, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Bawdy Tales, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Bear for Punishment, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Beast Alley, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Be Avant-Garde, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Beaver Films, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Beauty Knows No Pain, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Bed and Sofa, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Before Hindsight, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Before the Revolution, 1964, (4 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 3 to 6)
    - Be Gone, Dull Care, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Behind the Veil, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - die beispiellose verteidigung der Festung Deutschkreutz, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Belle de Jour, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bells of Atlantis, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Ingmar Bergman, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Berlin, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Beschin Meadows (Bezhin Lug), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - The Best of May, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - The Best of Your Life, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Bethune, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Betty Tells Her Story, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Between Two Worlds, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Beyond the Law, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Les Biches, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Il Bidone, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Bierkampf, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Big Business, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - A Bigger Splash, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - The Big Heat, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Big Knife, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Big Shave, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Billabong, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Binary Bit Patterns, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Birch Wood, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Birds, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - The Birds, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Birds of Paradise, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Birds, Orphans and Fools, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Birth and Death, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - The Birth Film, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Birth without Violence, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Bitter Grapes, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - The Bitter Tears of Petra von Kant, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Black and White Burlesque, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - The Black God and the White Devil, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Black Natchez, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Black on White, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Black Panthers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Black Peter, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Blanche, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Blond Cobra, 1959-1963 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Blood of the Condor (Yawar Mallku), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - The Blood of a Poet, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - The Blood of the Beasts, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Blow-Job, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Blow-Up, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - The Blue Angel, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Blue Jeans, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - The Blue Light, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Blue Movie, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Bob & Carol & Ted & Alice, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - The Bodysnatcher, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Bondi, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Le Bonheur, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Borinage, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - A Boring Afternoon, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Le Boucher, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Paul Bowles in the Land of the Jumblies, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Boy, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Brand X, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Brandy in the Wilderness, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Braverman's Condensed Cream of Beatles, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Brazil: A Report on Torture, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Breakfast, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Breathing, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Breathing Together: Revolution of the Electric Family, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Breathless, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Brewster McCloud, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bridges Go Round, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Brother Carl, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Lenny Bruce: A Performance, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Brummer's, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Brutality in Stone, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The Burmese Harp, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Burn!, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Busby Berkeley Excerpts (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Buster Keaton Rides Again, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - But Do Not Deliver Us From Evil, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Butterflies Do Not Live Here, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - By the Law, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Le Cadeau, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - The Cage, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Les Cages (Klatki), 1967 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Camps of the Dead, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Ah Ca Ira, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Calcutta, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - The California Reich, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Callot Fecit, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Calma, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Calvary, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - The Calypso Singer, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Camarades, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - The Cameraman, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Camille without Camellias, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Campamento, 1970s (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Canadian Pacific, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - The Cannibals, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Canterbury Tales, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Canyon, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Capricci, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Capricious Summer, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Caressed, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Carnal Knowledge, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Carriage to Vienna, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - The Casting, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Castle of Purity, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Castro Street, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - The Cat and the Canary, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Catch, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - The Cat People, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Cat People, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - The Cats (Kattorna), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - A Cat, Two Women and One Man, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - The Ceiling, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Celine and Julie Go Boating, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - The Ceremony, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - The Ceremony, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Chairmen, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - A Chairy Tale, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The Changing Rains, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Changing, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Un Chant D'Amour, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Charlie Chaplin: Keystone Cops, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Charlie Chaplin: Shorts, 1915-1917 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - The Chaplain Revue, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Charge and Countercharge, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Charleen or How Long Has This Been Going On?, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Charmides, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Chartres Cathedral, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Charmed Particles, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Charm of Life, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Charulata, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Chasidim, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Chasse aux Mouches, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Une Chaumiere et un Coeur, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - The Chelsea Girls, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Chess Games with Marcel Duchamp, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Un Chien Andalou, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Chikamatzu Monogatari (Crucified Lovers), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Chicken Soup, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - The Childhood of Maxim Gorky, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - The Children Are Watching Us, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Chimes at Midnight, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - China Is Near, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Chinese Checkers, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Chinese Firedrill, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - La Chinoise, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Choose Life, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Chotyn, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Christo: Valley Curtain, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Christo: Wrapped Coast, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - The Chronicle of Anna Magdelena Bach, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Ciao, Federico, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Le Cinematograph, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - The Cinematographer, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Cinetracts, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - The Circus, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Citizen Kane, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - City Lights, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - City of Women, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Claire's Knee, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Cléo: Between 5 and 7, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - La Cloche, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - A Clockwork Orange, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Closely Watched Trains, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Close-Up, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Cloth, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Clowns, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Co-Co Puffs, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Cold Cows Waiting, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - To Collect Evidence, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Color Me Shameless, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - The Color of Pomegranates, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Columbus of Sex, 1970s (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Coming Apart, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Coming Attractions, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Commando 52, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Communists on Campus, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Competition, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Computer Generated 3D Kinetic Sculpture and Ballet, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Computer Symposium and Films, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Computer Film Conference 1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Comrades, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - La Concentration, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Concert in X Minor, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Concerto Pour un Exil, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - The Confession, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Conflagration (Enjo), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - The Conformist, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - The Confrontation, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Constitution and Censorship, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Contempt, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Contrepied, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Conversations in Vermont, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Cool Hand Luke, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Les Corbeaux, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Corps Profund, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - La Corrida Interdite, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Corridor, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Cortile Cascino, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - The Age of Cosimo de Medici, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Cosmic Ray, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Cosmic Zoom, [1968] (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Cosmos, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Courage for Every Day (Kazdy Den Odvahu), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - The Crazy Ray, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Les Creatures, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - The Cremator (Spalorac Mrtvol), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Cries and Whispers, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - The Criminal Life of Archibald de la Cruz, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Crisis: Behind a Presidential Commitment, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Critic, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Crocus, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Crossings and Meetings, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Crossroads for America, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - The First Cry (Krik), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - The Cry of Jazz, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Cuba, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - The Cuckoo Waltz, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - The Cure, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Curse of the Cat People, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Cybele, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - The Cycle, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Cycles, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Cynthia's Ceremony, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Dada, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Daisies, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - The Damned, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - A Dancer's World, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Dance Chromatic, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Dangling Participle, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Danish Blue, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Dans L'Engrenage, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - David Holzman's Diary, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - David: Off and On, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Day after Trinity, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - A Day at the Races, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Daybreak Express, 1954-1963 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Day for Night, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - A Day in the City (En Dag I Staden), 1956 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - A Day in the Country, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Day of Freedom, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Day of Wrath, 1943, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Days of 36, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Days and Nights in the Forest, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Days of Rage, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Days of Water, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - A Day with Timmy Page, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Dead, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dead of Night, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dead Youth, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Deadline for Action, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Deal, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Dear Irene, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Dear John, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Death by Hanging, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Death in Venice, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Death of a Bureaucrat, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Death of a Flea Circus Director, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - The Death of Mao, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Death of Maria Malibran, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Deathday, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Death Ray (Kuleshov), 1925 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Death Row, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Deathstyles, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Death to the Invader, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Deathwish, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Simone de Beauvoir, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - The Decameron, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Deep End, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Deep Throat, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Deer Hunter, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Demonstrantenselbstschutze, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Le Départ, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - The Deserter and the Nomads, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Deserters USA, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Destiny, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Destroy, She Said, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Les Deux Timides, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Devils, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Dew Drop, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Diabolique, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Diamonds of the Night, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Diary of a Lost Girl, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Diary of a Moonlighter, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Diary of a Shinjuku Burglar, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Diary of a Yunbogi Boy, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Jeanne Diehlman, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Dinner at Eight, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Dinner Three Minutes, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Directed by John Ford, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - La Direction d'Acteur par Jean Renoir, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Director and His Actor Look at Footage, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Dirty Books, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoisie, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Disorder, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Disparates, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Distant Journey, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Divided Sky, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - The Doctor's Dream, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Strangelove, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Nudity, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Dodes' Ka-Den, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Dom, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Don Giovanni, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Don Quixote, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Don't Cry with Your Mouth Full, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Don't Look Now, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - The Door in the Wall, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Double Suicide, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - The Dove, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Down By the Riverside, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Do You Have a Lion at Home?, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Dreams and Nightmares, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Dreams that Money Can Buy, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Dream of Wild Horses, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Dressed to Kill, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Drive, He Said, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Duck Soup, 1933, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Duet for Cannibals, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Dunmovin, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Dyn Amo, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Eakins, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Earth, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Easy Street, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Eaten Horizons, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Eaux D'Artifice, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Early Works, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - The East Is Red, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Easyout, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Easy Rider, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Eat, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - An Eater, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Echoes of Silence, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Ecstasy, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - L'Eden et Apres, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - 8 ½, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Eika Katappa, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - El (This Strange Passion), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Electronic Labyrinth (THX 1138), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Elegy, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - El Salvador: Another Vietnam, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - El Salvador: Revolution or Death, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - El Salvador: The People's Victory, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - El Salvador Fact Clippings, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Eldridge Cleaver, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Elegy for Violence, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Elvira Madigan, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Emak Bakia, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Emitai, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Emperor Tomato Ketchup, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Empire, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - The Empire Strikes Back, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Encounters with Jung: Two Views, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - End of a Priest, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - End of a Revolution, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The End of August at Hotel Ozone, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The End of One, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - The End of St. Petersburg, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The End of Summer, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - End of the Art World, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Energy and Morality, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Les Enfants Terribles, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Enthusiasm, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Entr'acte, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - The Epic that Never Was, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Eraserhead, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Erection, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Max Ernst, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Eros + Massacre, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Best of the 1st Erotic Film Festival, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Les Escargots, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Maurits Escher: Painter of Fantasies, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Un Été Américain, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - The Eternal Jew, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - L'Etoile de Mer, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Etude, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Euphoria, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Europe After the Rain, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Even Dwarfs Started Small, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Every Man for Himself, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Every Man for Himself and God, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Every Seventh Child, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Everything for Sale, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Everything You Always Wanted To Know About Sex But Were Afraid To Ask, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Exchange of Words, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - The Exorcist, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - The Exterminating Angel, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Eyes Without a Face, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Eyewash, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - The Face, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Face of Another, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Faces, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Faces in Shadow, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Fährmann Maria, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The Fall, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - The Fall of the House of Usher (Epstein), 1928 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - The Fall of the House of Usher (Webber), 1928 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Family, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)